wifistudy.com 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy

In this policy, the words "we", "our", and "us" refer to WifiStudy and the privacy mechanism outlined identify personally identifiable or personal information that may be collected, how such information is used, and the choices you have regarding our use of this information.

In addition to the terms stated in Terms of Service provided under this Website, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Authorized representatives of WifiStudy on a need to know basis only use any information received from you. We constantly review our systems and data to secure your personal information. We will investigate any complaint or such actions with a view to prosecuting and/or taking civil proceedings to recover damages against those responsible. Any User who does not agree with any provisions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service is required to leave the Website immediately. Should you disagree with policy and still continue to access the Website and provide your personal information, WifiStudy disclaim all the liabilities arising therefrom.

#### Applicability

This privacy policy applies to all Users who access the Website and are therefore required to read and understand the privacy policy before submitting any Personal Information. If you have inadvertently submitted any such information to WifiStudy prior to reading the privacy statements set out herein, and you do not agree with the manner in which such information is collected, stored or used, then you may access, modify and delete all information stored about You by writing to us at [support@WifiStudy.com](mailto:support@WifiStudy.com). WifiStudy is keeping personal data of the User, and every User is also entitled to require WifiStudy to delete and destroy all such information (but not that of other Users).

This privacy policy applies to Website and services that are owned and operated by WifiStudy. WifiStudy does not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within its Services. Third party websites may place their own cookies or other files on the Users' computer, collect data or solicit personal information from the Users, for which WifiStudy is not responsible or liable. Accordingly, WifiStudy does not make any representations concerning the privacy practices or policies of such third parties or terms of use of such websites, nor does WifiStudy guarantee the accuracy, integrity, or quality of the information, data, text, software, sound, photographs, graphics, videos, messages or other materials available on such websites. The inclusion or exclusion does not imply any endorsement by WifiStudy of the website, the website's provider, or the information on the website. WifiStudy encourages the User to read the privacy policies of that Website.

WifiStudy has taken all reasonable precautions to treat Personal Information as confidential with industry standards that it has implemented to protect from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, modification and unlawful destruction or accidental loss of the Personal Information.

#### Access

User are allowed to access the Website, register for courses and avail Services available with WifiStudy as a guest and without creating an account on the Website or providing any Personal Information, WifiStudy takes no responsibility or validate the information provided by the guest, except as otherwise required under any law, regulation or an order of competent authority. In order to have access to all the features and benefits on our Website, a User is required to first create an account on our Website. To create an account a User is required to provide the Personal Information as may be required during the time of registration. Other information requested on the registration page, including the ability to receive promotional offers from WifiStudy, is optional. WifiStudy may, in future, include other optional requests for information from the User to help WifiStudy to customize the Website to deliver personalized information to the User. Without User's agreement, WifiStudy will not share, rent or sell any personal information with third parties in any way other than what is disclosed in this privacy policy. WifiStudy may keep records of telephone calls received and made for making enquiries, registered courses, feedback or other purposes for the purpose of rendering services effectively and efficiently.

#### Personal Information

Personal Information shall mean the information which identifies the User, name, identification number email address, age, phone number, password or any financial account information provided to WifiStudy at the time of registration or any time thereafter.

#### Automatic Information Collection

Our system collects information that is sent over the internet without your control. Some examples of the information we collect and analyse include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet; login; email; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; course enrolled history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other users to create features, reports such as popular courses, most used features etc; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click stream to, and from our website, including date and time; cookie number; courses or videos you viewed or searched for; the phone number you used to call our customer service.

During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain page, course and videos, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

#### Information Security

To protect the security of your Personal information during transmission, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. To prevent unauthorized access to sensitive information, it is important for you to monitor those who have access to your password and to your computer, laptop or any other device through which your account can be accessed. Be sure to sign off when finished while using a shared computer.

#### Use of your personal information

While availing our services you will provide access to WifiStudy with your personal information. If that information is wrong, you can request us to modify or delete the same. WifiStudy will take all reasonable measures to ensure that the information is modified and used for rendering services to you and as otherwise in compliance with laws. When editing or deleting personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. WifiStudy may at its discretion reject any request that is contrary to law, requires un-reasonable technical efforts. We do not assure that we will delete all residual copies and archives made by any third party without our knowledge and consent.

#### Exceptions

Your Personal Information may be shared with third parties who have a need or authority to receive such information, if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to comply with (i) in response to any authority having to receive such information under law (ii) any order of court (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of WifiStudy, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

#### User choices with regard to access of information

WifiStudy does not make any unsolicited calls or otherwise market any products or services, except for in relation to the purpose for which such information has been provided or taking any feedback or addressing the complaints. User shall not disclose their Personal Information to any third Parties not authorised by WifiStudy and verify the identity of such personal who seek information. WifiStudy will communicate with the Users through email and notices posted on the Website or through other means available through the service, including text and other forms of messaging. The Users can change their e-mail and contact preferences at any time by logging into their account or by calling the customer support or such or mode available from time to time.

WifiStudy may, if you so choose, send direct mailers to you at the address given by you. You have the option to 'opt-out' of this direct mailer by way of links provided at the bottom of each mailer. We respect your privacy and to the extent that you choose not to receive such mailers, we will take all steps to remove you from the list. Should you evidence any violation of our terms and policies, please write to us at support@WifiStudy.com or call us at our call center and report such incident.

All the information provided to WifiStudy either by a User, the User confirms that the same including sensitive personal information, is true, accurate and voluntary. User has the right to withdraw information at any time, in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy and the Terms of Service.

#### Report, Analysis & Confidentiality

WifiStudy may have to use Personal Information without reference to any persona or identity for research, statistical analysis and business intelligence purpose and may transfer such research, statistical or intelligence data in an aggregated or non-personally identifiable form to third parties and affiliates.

All WifiStudy employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of sensitive personal data or information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of every User's sensitive personal data and information.

#### Sharing of Information

WifiStudy may also disclose or transfer User's personal and other information which a User provides, to another third party as part of reorganization or a sale of the assets of WifiStudy corporation division or company. Any third party to which WifiStudy transfers or sells its assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that a User provide to us.

To the extent necessary to provide Users with the services on the Website, WifiStudy may provide their Personal Information to third party contractors who work on behalf of or with WifiStudy to provide Users with such services, to help WifiStudy communicate with Users or to maintain the Website. Generally, these contractors do not have any independent right to share this information, however certain contractors who provide services on the Website, including the providers of online communications services, will have rights to use and disclose the personal information collected in connection with the provision of these services in accordance with their own privacy policies.

#### Revision of terms & Grievance reporting

WifiStudy may update or amend this privacy policy at any time, with or without advance notice. In the event there are significant changes in the way WifiStudy treats User's personally identifiable information, WifiStudy will display a notice on the Website or send Users an email. WifiStudy's current privacy policy applies to all information that WifiStudy has about Users and their account.

Notwithstanding the above, WifiStudy shall not be required to notify the Users of any changes made to the privacy policy. Should you have any concern or reject the changes in the privacy policy you can refuse to accept the amendments and opt for withdrawing your Personal Information by writing to us at support@WifiStudy.com. 

If you have any compliant or grievances with respect to Website or this Privacy Policy please write to us at support@WifiStudy.com.
